addnewfriends.com 2006-12-05

# MySpace Bot, Friend Blaster Pro - Start growing your MySpace Friends with the #1 MySpace Friend Adder program!

******** **Privacy Policy**

_Note:_ _This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. Continued access of AddNewFriends.com LLC by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy._

It is the goal of AddNewFriends.com LLC to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. The following is a summary of the various ways we treat the information you provide us while using our site. 

AddNewFriends.com LLC generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information, such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. 

AddNewFriends.com LLC uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you request information about one of our services, we will use the information you provide to contact you with the information you requested. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. 

AddNewFriends.com LLC will never sell your personal information. We also do not share information with our affiliates. 

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies minimally to maintain state while you use our web site. 

Our cookies may, but typically do not, contain personally identifiable information. 

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. 

If you don't want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of AddNewFriends.com LLC may not function as designed. 

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

Use our **contact** page if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
